dfeldman@awwa.org

SUMMARY

Talented digital content producer with strong professional and educational background in print and web design. Keen understanding of technology, management of digital systems and assets, and adaptation of content across platforms. Proven experience managing projects and supporting association staff to reach goals.

CORE QUALIFICATIONS

- Master of Science degree candidate in Information, Communication and Technology, with concentration in web design and development
- Production specialization in graphic and web design, editorial production, and multimedia content
- Experience researching, managing, and analyzing complex projects to fulfill business requirements
- Trusted team partner that supports, educates, and trains staff to find outstanding project solutions
- Self-starter with strong work ethic and drive to create business improvements and efficiencies
- Excellent verbal and written communication skills

EXPERIENCE

American Water Works Association | Denver, Colo.

2007-Present

Design and manage digital content production for an extensive range of association projects, while maintaining reliable excellence of deliverables. Train staff on new technologies, workflows, and job skills.

Senior Graphic Designer (2014-Present)

Responsible for creative direction, graphic production, and website design of Journal AWWA.

- Review and manage production of in-house and contract graphic design
- Create artwork concepts, illustration, and article layouts
- Design and update Journal AWWA website content
- Train staff in technical illustration and publishing workflows
- Author graphic submission requirements and periodical style guides

Production Editor (2011-2014)

Managed graphic design production cycles of Opflow magazine.

- Designed layouts and technical illustrations to meet specifications
- Provided quality assurance for advertisers, printers, and staff
- Assisted in writing, proofing, and editing content

Guided art direction and design for launch of IDA Journal and Section Newsletters.

- Created brand identity and promotional collateral for international publications
- Produced content layout, technical illustrations, artwork, and page impositions

Additional achievements:

- Introduced and trained publications staff on InCopy/InDesign editorial workflow
- Steered Just One Thing committee to help create the Lunch & Learn initiative
- Exceeded job requirements in annual reviews for three years

Graphic Designer (2007-2011)

Collaborated with creative, editorial, marketing, and sales teams to produce varied association media.

- Produced direct mail, house ads, web banners, animation and rich media content
- Managed and designed graphic production of Opflow magazine
- Photographed product shots, staff, and company events for promotional collateral

Webmaster | Colorado Art Education Association | Denver, Colo.

2000-2007

Performed website design and maintenance for the largest art education association in Colorado.

- Incepted first website design and brand identity for the association
- Routinely created and updated web content
- Designed annual conference programs online and in print
- Worked with developer to add database functionality to website
- Managed server migrations

dfeldman@awwa.org

EXPERIENCE (Cont.)

Graphic Designer | North American Directory Services | Loveland, Colo.

2003-2005

Graphic design position with publisher of hospitality-based business directories. Produced a high volume of designs and ads for businesses throughout North America. Responsibilities included design and illustration, managing proofing stages, and digital prepress management.

Graphic Designer | 601 Design | Denver, Colo.

2001-2002

Graphic design position with award-winning local design studio. Completed various print, layout, typesetting, design and illustration projects.

EDUCATION

- MS Information, Communication and Technology, web design and development concentration University of Denver, University College, Denver, Colo.
 Expected graduation in spring 2017, currently carrying 4.0 GPA Coursework includes:
 - Graduate Research and Writing
 - ICT Business Foundations
 - o ICT Technical Foundations
 - o Enterprise Architecture
 - o Web-enabled Information Systems
 - o Website Design and Management
 - o Advanced Website Design and Management
 - Usability Design for Websites
 - o Mobile Application Development with Web Standards
 - o XML & Data in Application Development
 - Web Scripting with JavaScript
 - Web Analytics
 - o ICT Capstone Project
- BFA, graphic design concentration, 2000 Colorado State University, Fort Collins, Colo.

SKILLS

- Advanced proficiency:
 - o InDesign
 - Photoshop
 - Illustrator
- Intermediate proficiency:
 - o Microsoft Office 365
 - o HTML
 - CSS
 - JavaScript
 - o Flash
 - Dreamweaver
 - WordPress
- Working knowledge:
 - Microsoft SharePoint
 - o DNN

CERTIFICATION

UI/UX Design Transitions Certificate Program Boulder Digital Arts, Boulder, Colo., 2014